enterforgifts.com 2010-09-15

# None

EnterForGifts.com understands how important your privacy is to you, so we are committed to assuring your privacy. This Privacy Policy ("policy") tells users ("you" or "applicant") of the website and the services provided therein about the information collected and how we use and share this information. Please keep in mind that through our website, you may be interacting with third parties that operate under their own privacy and security policies. This policy only addresses our website. Other sites accessible through our website and companies to whom your information is transferred have their own privacy policies and disclosures. Please consult each website’s privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies of third parties. 

## What information do we collect?

EnterForGifts.com collects two types of information about our users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

EnterForGifts.com collects several types of information that may identify a particular individual ("personally identifiable information"). We collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us through your use of our website, such as by sending questions to us via the website or email. The type of personally identifiable information we collect include: name, email address. 

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-personally identifiable information refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our website in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet. 

## Information Collected by Third Parties

We may allow third parties, including advertising partners to display advertisements on our website. These companies may use tracking technologies, including cookies, to collect information about users of our website who view or interact with these advertisements. 

## How we use information we collect

We will use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our website, provide you with customer support, verify or review your application information to determine whether it meets eligibility requirements, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze website use and behavior, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our website’s content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreements with you, including our Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy. We may also use your information to communicate with you by email about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our marketing partners, or other third parties. Your information may also be used by us or by third parties to whom we transfer it to provide the products or services you have requested. 

When you use our website we store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our website. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Website stores on your computer that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. The cookies make your use of the website easier, make the website run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure website. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our website may not work properly in that case. 

## With whom do we share your information?

We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy and applicable state and federal law. We provide the products and services offered on our website through contractual arrangements with affiliates, advertisers, participating lenders, service providers, and other third parties. 

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers’ orders, traffic patterns, and related website information to third party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information. 

Occasionally we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate government authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. 

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending us a e-mail with your detailed unsubscribe request to info@enterforgifts.com. Please be aware it may take up to 10 business days to remove your name. You should also be aware that unsubscribing from us will not automatically unsubscribe you from third parties’ lists and/or databases. 

## Privacy Policies of Third Parties

When you sign-up for services through our website, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policies. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses our use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our website, and companies to whom your information is transferred, have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our website may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. You should also be aware that unsubscribing from us will not automatically unsubscribe you from third parties’ lists and/or databases. 

## Business transitions

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information (both Personally Identifiable and Non-Personally Identifiable Information) may be one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired, such customer information will be included within the transferred assets. 

## Changes to our policy

We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it frequently. 

If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy, please do not access or use this website.
